<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>classwork | Elias Stengel-Eskin</title>
    <link>/category/classwork/</link>
      <atom:link href="/category/classwork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>classwork</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>classwork</title>
      <link>/category/classwork/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack For Instructors</title>
      <link>/hci/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/hci/project1/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;div id=&#34;ariel-bao-cameron-franz-elias-stengel-eskin&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ariel Bao, Cameron Franz, Elias Stengel-Eskin&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;background&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, many aspects of life including education have moved to a largely online setting. This has created new challenges but also new opportunities for streamlining and improving educational experiences. The Slack platform is incredibly popular in modern office spaces and offers rapid and efficient communication, we believe that with some minor changes, it could provide and integrated educational environment that enriches student-instructor interactions. In particular, the rapid feedback available through Slack might provide a suitable proxy for face-to-face communication while accommodating individuals facing the myriad additional challenges of teaching and studying from home (e.g. different timezones, unreliable internet, personal responsiblities, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this project, we focus on the perspective of the instructor, as in a course the instructor typically plays a more active role with the students largely acting as consumers. Our product is designed for a modified course structure, which has been adjusted for remote learning. Students are expected to watch pre-recorded lectures on their own time, and there are mandatory 1-hour office-hour-style discussion periods once a week. Each week has two lectures. The course has 3 assignments and 2 group projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;contextual-inquiry&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Contextual inquiry&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;subject&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Subject&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;contextual inquiry&lt;/em&gt; was conducted with a student with TA-ing experience who has used Slack in the past, but not extensively. We opted to use a contextual inquiry for our user research, as this best puts us in the shoes of someone using Slack for teaching while concomitantly allowing us to build a better persona of the instructor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intents&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Intents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol style=&#34;list-style-type: decimal&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create an assignment and share it with all students 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IOaJJO_02zo&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vChONkF07zM&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Send each student their graded assignment with feedback 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hLidERXSoDY&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lhRLNIUDgfo&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assign students to groups for the group project 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z4GxzMarT2o&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dgxGqNcylZY&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assign each group a topic 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bEljMZ2F018&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6_hfccsCzlc&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create a discussion thread for the weekly office hour and send students a required reading for that week’s office hour 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/i5NKk7XoHIw&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/SqOs1DMhrb4&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;persona-1-instructor&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Persona 1: Instructor&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on our CI and background knowledge, we propose the following persona for an instructor: The instructor has multiple responsibilities, of which teaching is only one. Despite the changes associated with remote learning, the instructor endeavours to provide the best possible experience for their students. Thus, efficiency is of paramount importance to the instructor; they are ready to devote time to their course, but want to minimize the amount of time spent on tedious non-teaching activities. Furthermore, the instructor is cognizant of the different cirumstances under which students are learning this semester. The instructor is familiar with Slack&#39;s interfaces and is computer-literate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;ideation-and-analysis&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ideation and Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;channels-were-used-for-groups-and-assignments&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Channels were used for Groups and Assignments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;SlackExampleImage.png&#34; alt=&#34;Slack Image&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;A classroom slack environment with relevant areas circled&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We found that channels (circled in blue) were used for making groups and creating discussion around assignments. To create a channel, the instructor clicks the Add Channel button (green circle). A channel dedicated to sending assignments to students was relatively fast: the instructor simply creates a channel and has it automatically add everyone. Using channels for groups was more tedious. For each group, the instructor needed to click “Add Channel” and type the name of everyone in the group. This means that the instructor would need to create their groups somewhere else (like Excel) and then do a bunch of copy and pasting or typing, even though all of the names are already in Slack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that it should be easier to automatically populate channels with randomly assigned groups in a way that minimizes instructor effort while maximizing flexibility. Furthermore, given the increased number of students who are learning remotely from all over the world, we believe that any changes should natively support grouping students by timezone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;direct-messages-were-used-to-give-feedback-to-students&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Direct messages were used to give feedback to students&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Direct messages were used for giving grades and feedback. For each student the instructor would: click on that student, paste a message like “You got a 95%, my feedback is X”, edit that message, and then send the DM. Doing this for each student is obviously tedious, and it does beg a further question: does the instructor have their grades and feedback in some other document (like Excel) and is pasting them over? Or are they going to each student, grading their assignment, and sending messages as they go? In the Excel case it is a lot of copying and pasting to send a DM to every student, and being able to automatically send templated messages from a spreadsheet would be useful. In the grading-as-they-go case, keeping track of who has been graded would be tedious. In our first CI we did not get far enough into the details of how an instructor grades work to answer this question. Yet we can guess from platforms like Gradescope that instructors like to type out their grade and feedback once without having to later copy and paste into some other platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that if Slack is to be used for classroom interactions, there should be an easy-to-use interface for managing and updating coursework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;finding-information-involved-a-lot-of-browsing-for-students&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Finding information involved a lot of browsing for students&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also looked at the Slack classroom from the perspective of a student. In finding out what they need to do, we found that our volunteer student traveled broadly around the Slack classroom. They clicked on multiple channels (the bold ones that indicated unread messages) to look for any relevant new information. They clicked on the channel relevant to their assignment and looked for the original information from the instructor. In general we found that the student, who was using Slack for iOS, was swiping back and forth between the channel menu and the messages area often. They also had to scroll far up in the assignment info to find the pinned information from the instructor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;SlackDiagram1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Slack Diagram&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Diagram of how the user performed the various actions during the contextual inquiries&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to minimize the amount of time spent by students traveling between features, we propose adding shortcuts to the interface which allow students to rapidly jump past pinned information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;prototypes-and-testing&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Prototypes and Testing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We developed our prototypes using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.figma.com/&#34;&gt;figma&lt;/a&gt; software, building off of Slack templates by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.figmacrush.com/slack-ui-template-figma/&#34;&gt;figmacrush&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;initial-prototype-description&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Initial Prototype Description&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;featureShowcase.png&#34; alt=&#34;Feature showcase&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Introducing users to new features is crucial. Here we have a popup that describes the feature, shows where it is, and provides an obvious button to click. Visibility is guaranteed by slightly graying out the rest of the screen.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;studentList.png&#34; alt=&#34;student list&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;After clicking the button to create a team, the instructor is presented with this screen. Here the instructor can set their preferences for &lt;em&gt;automatic&lt;/em&gt; group creation — no tedious typing required. Crucially the automatic grouping takes into account time zone, which is a factor that instructors have to consider. If the automatic grouping does not take into account a factor important to the instructor then the instructor will have to adjust the groups later. This can be done later &lt;em&gt;without&lt;/em&gt; more typing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;timeZones.png&#34; alt=&#34;time zones&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Here the instructor can see the automatically created groups, and adjust them by dragging names around. Overflow is dealt with by “expand” buttons, though scrolling would also work&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;congrats.png&#34; alt=&#34;congrats&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;The nice animation played here is intended to make the user feel good about using the new feature, although we acknowledge that the actual experience of using the feature will be the main determiner of whether they use it again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;todoList.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo list&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;This is a different feature, also accessible from the main slack sidebar. Here the instructor can find their schedule for things they need to do related to the groups and the assignments. Submission statistics are shown for assignments. Ideally grading would also be possible within the interface somewhere, as having to download files or copy and paste is troublesome. The assignment statistics, which drop down after clicking the little plus, also lead to the ability to schedule reminders for students.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;scheduledMeeting.png&#34; alt=&#34;scheduled meeting&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Here the instructor can schedule a reminder about the assignment to be sent to students at a specific time. We separate date and time so that there’s not a single date picker switching between calendar and clock.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;scroll.png&#34; alt=&#34;scrolling&#34; /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Here we provide an interface for the student to quickly find information from their instructor. Clicking on the (i) in the top right will immediately scroll the student to the informational post from the instructor, and clicking the calendar icon will scroll the user back to the most recent messages.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;usability-evaluation&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Usability Evaluation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For each feature, we conducted &lt;strong&gt;formative&lt;/strong&gt; usability tests with a different subject than was used in the CI. The subject for usability testing is an experienced teacher who currently teaches at the middle and high-school level, and is familiar with teaching in a remote-learning environment. The goals of the first evaluation are to assess the usability of the prototypes with respect to the CI, and to identify any shortcomings to address in further rounds of prototyping. The participant was told that she would be asked to perform a number of tasks on a new software, and that she should do her best and to think out loud. After testing, the subject was debriefed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;managing-assignments&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Managing assignments&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/PQ4E8ytYptc&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;creating-groups&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Creating groups&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BJBonA0pb0A&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;scrolling-to-pinned-messages&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Scrolling to pinned messages&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IUXRO_3EehQ&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;second-round-ideation-and-prototyping&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Second-round Ideation and Prototyping&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the results of the formative testing, we determined that the product would benefit from additional features. Primarily, in the debrief, the subject expressed a desire for increased flexibility regarding the content of the reminder message sent to students. This feature was added and a final round of &lt;strong&gt;summative&lt;/strong&gt; testing was performed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;summative-evaluation&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Summative evaluation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jF6vhUzolAk&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;ux-evaluation&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;UX evaluation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To go beyond our evaluations, we conducted a &lt;strong&gt;user experience evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; using a &lt;strong&gt;Likert scale&lt;/strong&gt; questionnaire. This format of post-hoc evaluation allows us to gain deeper insights into the usability of the product and its general impression on the subject after giving them some time to reflect. The questionnaire is available &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfmkVK9W8FfRwnmG3zhlREp0g39B3Zl27Wjh4ecI2MDOiK7xQ/viewform?usp=sf_link&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;ux-results&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;UX results&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The average score for questions was 4.6/5, with 5 being &amp;quot;strongly agree&amp;quot; and 1 being &amp;quot;strongly disagree.&amp;quot; All questions were positive, so we take this as a good sign that our product was easy to use. The following statements received ratings below 5/5: - &amp;quot;The assignment management interface was easy to find&amp;quot; - &amp;quot;It was clear how to send a reminder to students who hadn&#39;t completed the assignment&amp;quot; - &amp;quot;The function to create an assignment was easy to find&amp;quot; - &amp;quot;It was easy to scroll to a pinned message&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These represent directions for further improvements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;conclusions&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Conclusions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have presented a number of features for developing Slack into a standalone platform for teaching courses remotely. We believe that our features touch on many of the issues that were observed in the CI portion. Specifically, we have opted to focus on creating and managing assignments and groups, which is integral to the teaching process, especially as remote classes tend to prefer assignments over exams. Some of the strengths of our approach include our high-fidelity prototypes, the attention to detail in our assignment creation interface especially with respect to creating an equitable learning environment for those learning from other timezones, and our multiple iterations of prototyping and evaluation. Limitations include increased reliance on a single platform, which may make classes more uniform and less flexible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HCI Assignment 1</title>
      <link>/hci/assignment1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/hci/assignment1/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;div id=&#34;hci-assignment-1-improving-basic-functionality-of-myjhu&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;HCI Assignment 1: Improving basic functionality of myJHU&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Graduate students at JHU are faced with a unique challenge of being both students and employees. This means navigating both the standard student-facing sites for registering for classes and checking grades, like SIS and Blackboard, but also employee interfaces such as ESS. Many of these interfaces are available throught the myJHU portal, but learning how to efficiently use the portal takes time. If there&#39;s one thing graduate students don&#39;t have, it&#39;s time to waste figuring out where to find different features in myJHU. While we agree that myJHU provides a valuable service as an aggregator and portal for the variety of services available to graduate students, the interface itself can be clunky and difficult to use. In this assignment, we will endeavour to redesign the interface, optimizing for customizability and speed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;contextual-inquiry&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Contextual inquiry&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To this end, we performed a contextual inquiry to determine which interfaces were most in need of a redesign, and how actual users interact with myJHU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;subject&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Subject&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the purposes of this assignment, rather than recruiting a JHU graduate student, whose experience is colored by having used the interface many times before, we opted to recruit a non-JHU student who would act as a proxy for a brand new JHU graduate student using the interface for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intents&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Intents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since myJHU is a fairly well-designed page to begin with, we opted to test more intents and narrow down what we would change later on, based on what we saw in our contextual inquiry. These intents were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol style=&#34;list-style-type: decimal&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change profile name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find a book in the library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find Concur system for travel reimbursements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change what you see upon login&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check email&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on our inquiry, we opted to further analyze and re-design the page for intents 1, 3, and 4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;contextual-inquiry-recording&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Contextual inquiry recording&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/t-T2UdpU3hI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intent-1-change-profile-name&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Intent 1: Change profile name&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often, new students are assigned a profile with their full legal name, but have a different name that they go by. The following shows the sequential model of our subject attempting to change her name in myJHU:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;intent1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;700&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;results&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the subject was able to find the functions to change the profile easily enough, the save button was all the way at the bottom and took time to find. Another time-waster was two-factor authetication, but for security reasons, this understandably cannot be removed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intent-2-find-concur&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Intent 2: Find Concur&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concur is only one of the services available to grad students through myJHU, which we use as a proxy for finding services in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;intent2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;700&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;results-1&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concur is buried under the &amp;quot;Travel&amp;quot; option in the sidebar, which the subject had to spend some time visually searching for on the screen. Given just the name (not knowing it is used for travel) it would be very difficult to find.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intent-3-customize-layout&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Intent 3: Customize Layout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The front page of myJHU has news and alerts about various topics at JHU and is spread out over a large area. Students should be able to customize what they see based on what they value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;intent3.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;700&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;results-2&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This turned out to be an impossible task. The subject first went down an incorrect path, assuming that the customization would be part of myProfile. After that, the subject tried to use the &amp;quot;configure&amp;quot; option, which only changes the sidebar. Finally, the subject gave up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;redesign&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Redesign&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address the breakdowns in the previous section, we propose a new, more compact site designed in &lt;a href=&#34;https://gomockingbird.com/&#34;&gt;Mockingbird&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;main.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intent-1-profile-changes&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Intent 1: Profile changes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We add a quick-link to change the profile directly under the profile picture. This opens a pop-out menu with the options of fields to change in the profile. &lt;img src=&#34;customize1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opening one of these menus changes the content of the pop-out to a list of editable fields. Contents can be discarded with the close button or saved with the large &amp;quot;confirm&amp;quot; button. &lt;img src=&#34;customize2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These popups allow the user to stay on the same page while updating their information, and update only small parts of their info at a time. The small size of the interface places the &amp;quot;confirm&amp;quot; directly in the subject&#39;s view, where before it required a large amount of scrolling to get to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intent-2-open-concur&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Intent 2: Open Concur&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather than forcing the user to use the sidebar, we include a large searchar which can be quickly accessed. As the user types, results begin to be filtered in a quick-search style, until only the top result remains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;searchbar1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This interface cuts down on time wasted scrolling over the sidebar and attempting to deduce under which heading different services are located.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;intent-3-customize&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Intent 3: Customize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather than being spread out and taking up more than the screen, the news and info on the homepage is consolidated into multiple tabs, grouped by topic. This allows for faster access to important information, such as COVID19 updates. The tabs also provide an intuitive interface for customization that everyone is familiar with. Each tab has a close button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;customize1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pressing the close button opens a small prompt which asks the user whether they want to close the window just for the duration of their session, or make their change permanent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;customize2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This change allows the user to customize the homepage and re-order what they see based on what they care about. It also makes it obvious how to customize the page, which was unclear before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;evaluation&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Evaluation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the final evaluation, we see that each task took much less time and was more intuitive than before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TFyRLlrI6do&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
